vouchercodes.in 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimer - www.vouchercodes.in

**Disclaimer:**  Below are the terms and conditions that apply to all our users on this website [www.vouchercode.in](http://www.vouchercode.in/). You have to be about 18 years of age or above to create a user account on this website or to get pleasure from our discount coupons or gift vouchers. By clicking on any of the links that are available on this website, you have agreed to all our terms and conditions.

**Your Personal Data/Information:-**

**How We Take Your Personal Information From You-**

Information provided by you by filling forms, subscriptions, and newsletter at [www.vouchercodes.in](http://www.vouchercodes.in/) , all is saved and secured by us. We can also ask you for your personal information at that time when you report a problem through our website or our mobile App. We also keep your records when you contact us for feedback or query. For a better shopping experience, sometime we may also ask you to complete some sort of surveys. Information received from the use of installed App on your mobile phones is also transmitted location data or access our website to collect all sorts of information via your mobile data. Our mobile App is designed to save your location data even if you are not logged in. This location data includes latitude and longitude of your device, direction of your travelling along with the time of the location.

**What We Did With Your Personal Data-**

In order to use our website, you need to fill the registration form completely with all your legal personal information that are required by our website [www.vouchercodes.in](http://www.vouchercodes.in/). It’s our commitment that the data offered by you will be fully protected by us. As we are the single owner of the information collected on the website or via mobile app. We will never sell out, rent out or share any kind, of any personal information of any of the users. Somehow we can collect information from other different websites or database to craft your online shopping experience more delightful. By sharing a wide range of offers, deals and sale information, we make your shopping quite easy and cheap.   

**How We Can Save Your Personal Data-**

While submitting your personal information with us at the time of making a payment from our website, then such information is encrypted and protected with our own encryption software that assist your web browser automatically to encrypt the data before you send it to us. The data that we collect from you may be transferred to a destination located outside of the **European Economic Area ("EEA")**. After transferring the data, all the information is also stored here. By providing information via the website or Mobile App you specifically consent to such information being transferred outside of the EEA. Unfortunately, till now the transmission of information that are held via internet is not so completely secure and although we and our management team take all possible and reasonable steps to protect your personal data, but still we can’t give any kind of guarantee for the security of it. Any transmission of personal data to the Site is at your own risk.

**Third Party Links-**

All offers, deals and gift voucher links are directly redirected to the advertiser’s websites through third party links that are used by us on different networks or promotions. By clicking on any link you stand with our terms & conditions. We take all our privacy policies strictly and keep customer information safe and secure. Our website and Mobile Product has links of other sites. So please be aware that we are not having our hands in such sort of privacy issues of other sites. We always encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read all our privacy policies very carefully. These privacy policies are surely applies on the information collected by us through our Site or via Mobile App.

**Updating/removal of personal information-**

If any user wants to update or remove his/her personal data, then it’s your responsibility to inform us, so that our team will able to share the appropriate methods for the same. Orin any case, you didn’t want our any kind of service, then also you have to inform us to either remove, update or change your personal information. Please make sure that an archive copy of any kind of change in your personal data is provided to us that may be retained by us for our personal records and audits.  

**Customer’s Right-**

Our company makes every effort to make you feel relaxed and calm while using our website and attain a wide range of practices, procedures and systems with the relevant data protection legislation.  We are a registered company, as a data controller for the purposes of the Act with registration number U72200DL2014PTC267216. Our main concern is to use your personal data in accordance with the legal requirements, principles and best practice recommendations that the Act allows us to grant you various rights in concern with the processing of your personal data. For further information about your rights under this Act, the rules that we stick here is to collecting and storing your personal information, and how you can check your data records. As you have a right to receive a copy of the information that we hold about your personal information, by sending a simple request form in writing, to us at [www.vouchercodes.in](http://www.vouchercodes.in/) c/o Voucher Codes India Pvt. Ltd, 306, 3rd Floor, Welldone Tech Park, Sohna Road, Sector-48, 122018 (Gurgaon)

**How To Reach Us-**

If you have any kind of question regarding our services and website, then you can easily contact us at 0124- 4125533 or you can also send an e-mail at [info@vouchercodes.in](mailto:info@vouchercodes.in) mentioning all your issues or queries that you have while using our website. Alternatively, you can also write us at Voucher Codes India Pvt. Ltd, 306, 3rd Floor, Welldone Tech Park, Sohna Road, Sector-48, 122018 (Gurgaon)

**Cookies and Data** : We do not force any customer to register or subscribe with our website. All customers subscribed from this website will get promotional e mailers to keep them updated with latest offers. We do not sell any customer data in any case to anyone. While clicking on any link a cookie is stores in customers browser who is on auto removes between 15 to 90 days period. You can remove cookies anytime by using browser removal process.

## Popular Stores

### Never Miss!

The best voucher codes again!
